{
    "subject": "resource/Ethnic_Germans_in_Bolivia",
    "predicate": "ontology/language",
    "object": "resource/Spanish_language",
    "human_readable": "The language of Ethnic Germans in Bolivia is Spanish.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9860154390335083,
            "question": "Is Spanish the primary language of Ethnic Germans in Bolivia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.956516444683075,
            "question": "Are there any unique dialects or variations of Spanish spoken by Ethnic Germans in Bolivia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9028096199035645,
            "question": "What language do Ethnic Germans in Bolivia speak?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8950044512748718,
            "question": "What are the implications of speaking Spanish for the cultural identity of Ethnic Germans in Bolivia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8719325661659241,
            "question": "Do Ethnic Germans in Bolivia primarily speak German?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7811421751976013,
            "question": "What linguistic influences can be observed among Ethnic Germans in Bolivia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7193052172660828,
            "question": "What factors might have contributed to the prevalence of Spanish among Ethnic Germans in Bolivia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7105512022972107,
            "question": "How does the language situation of Ethnic Germans in Bolivia compare to that of other ethnic groups in the country?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7021541595458984,
            "question": "How does the language spoken by Ethnic Germans in Bolivia reflect their history?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20866461098194122,
            "question": "Can you describe the linguistic landscape of Bolivia in general?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The language of Ethnic Germans in Bolivia is Spanish.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6495_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How does the language spoken by Ethnic Germans in Bolivia reflect their history?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6495_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How does the language situation of Ethnic Germans in Bolivia compare to that of other ethnic groups in the country?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6495_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What factors might have contributed to the prevalence of Spanish among Ethnic Germans in Bolivia?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6495_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6495_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6495_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6495_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6495_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6495_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6495_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6495_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6495_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6495_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6495_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe text states that Standard German is the largest non-official language spoken in Bolivia by Ethnic Germans, not Spanish. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: According to the context provided, it mentions that there are immigrant languages spoken in Bolivia, including Standard German. While not explicitly stated as the primary language for ethnic Germans, given that Spanish is recognized as the official and widely used language throughout Bolivia, and considering the historical context of Mennonites (a group of ethnic Germans) living in Santa Cruz who speak a dialect of German called Plautdietsch but use Standard German for writing and reading, it can be inferred that the primary language for Ethnic Germans in Bolivia is Spanish."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\n     \"output\": \"no\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "There is no information provided suggesting that the language of ethnic Germans in Bolivia is Spanish. Instead, there are mentions of Standard German being spoken by some residents of Santa Cruz Department as an immigrant language in Bolivia.",
            "category": -1
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The provided text states that Standard German is the largest non-official language of Bolivia with about 160,000 speakers, and 70,000 of these speakers are Mennonites who speak a dialect of German called Plautdietsch.",
            "category": -1
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "According to the provided context information, Standard German (Plautdietsch) is spoken by 160,000 ethnic Germans in Bolivia, who use Standard German for writing and reading, not Spanish.",
            "category": -1
        }
    }
}